<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Setting-up Cloud9 on AWS Quick Start Workshop</title>
    <link>https://workshop.quickstart.awspartner.com/30_setup_cloud9.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Setting-up Cloud9 on AWS Quick Start Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://workshop.quickstart.awspartner.com/30_setup_cloud9/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fork Quick Start repo</title>
      <link>https://workshop.quickstart.awspartner.com/30_setup_cloud9/1_create_new_gitrepo.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://workshop.quickstart.awspartner.com/30_setup_cloud9/1_create_new_gitrepo.html</guid>
      <description>You must have a GitHub account to fork an exisitng repo. If you do not have an account create one by following these instructions Signing up for a new GitHub Account
 Make sure you are logged into your GitHub account
 Each Quick Start consist of a GitHub repo where all the contents of the Quick Start live. This repo is a private GitHub repo during the development phase and made public after launch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Start scaffolding</title>
      <link>https://workshop.quickstart.awspartner.com/30_setup_cloud9/20_create_scaffolding.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://workshop.quickstart.awspartner.com/30_setup_cloud9/20_create_scaffolding.html</guid>
      <description>The GitHub repository for the Autodesk Forge Quick Start includes the following folders:
 ci - Contains the configuration file and parameter files used for automated testing. templates - Contains the AWS CloudFormation templates for the Quick Start. The templates can be in .json or .yaml file formats. packages - Contains the Forge application that gets deployed as part of the Quick Start submodules - Used for any referenced Quick Starts that are configured as submodules of the Quick Start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using the Event Engine dashboard</title>
      <link>https://workshop.quickstart.awspartner.com/30_setup_cloud9/30_ee_dashboard.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://workshop.quickstart.awspartner.com/30_setup_cloud9/30_ee_dashboard.html</guid>
      <description>If you are doing this as as a self-paced exercise, skip this page.
  In a browser, go to the Event Engine dashboard page. Enter the 12 digit hash provided to your team and choose Accept Terms &amp;amp; Login.  On the next page, you&amp;rsquo;ll find a link to access the AWS Console and a link containing a Readme pointing to workshop instructions.  Go to the AWS console using the AWS Console link in your Event Engine dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setup Git CLI</title>
      <link>https://workshop.quickstart.awspartner.com/30_setup_cloud9/40_setup_github_cli.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://workshop.quickstart.awspartner.com/30_setup_cloud9/40_setup_github_cli.html</guid>
      <description>Through out this workshop, you will run GitHub commands from your Cloud9 workspace terminal window, to perform different operations on your GitHub repo.
By default, Cloud9 workspace comes installed with Git CLI. However, you need to configure it to use with your GitHub account.
Configure Git Profile In the terminal, run these two commands, one at a time, substituting your Git name and email address for USER_NAME and EMAIL_ADDRESS, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>